
const questions=[
    {
        question:"In HTML, tags that include both on and off tag are called",
        answer:"container tag",
        options:[
            "comment tag",
            "document tag",
            "container tag",
            "None of the above",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:2,
        question:"The latest HTML standard is",
        answer:"HTML 5.0",
        options:[
            "HTML 4.0",
            "HTML 5.0",
            "XML",
            "SGML",

        ]

    },
 
    {
        numb:3,
        question:"The href attribute in the link tag specifies the:",
        answer:"Destination of a link",
        options:[
            "Destination of a link",
            "Link",
            " Hypertext",
            "None of the above",

        ]

    },
 
   
    {
        numb:4,
        question:"<a> and </a> are the tags used for ______",
        answer:"Adding links to your page",
        options:[
            "Adding image",
            "Aligning text",
            " Audio-voiced text",
            "Adding links to your page",
           ]

    },
    {
        numb:5,
        question:"HTML Event Attributes onunload fires",
        answer:"When the browser window has been closed",
        options:[
            "When the browser window has been closed",
            "When the browser window is minimized",
            "When the browser window has changed focus to other window",
            "After the page is finished loading",

        ]

    },
    {
        numb:6,
        question:"HTML Form Events _____, fires the moment that the element loses focus.",
        answer:"onblur",
        options:[
            "onblur",
            "onfocus",
            "onchange",
            "onlostfocus",

        ]

    },
    {
        numb:7,
        question:"Twitter limits the number of characters per tweet is ?",
        answer:"140",
        options:[
            "130",
            "160",
            "124",
            "140",

        ]

    },
    {
        numb:8,
        question:"What is cell padding?",
        answer:"Used to separate cell walls from their contents",
        options:[
            "Used to separate cell walls from their contents",
            "Used to set space between cells",
            "Both a and b above",
            "Used to provide width to a cell",

        ]

    },
    {
        numb:9,
        question:"What are meta tags used for?",
        answer:"To store information usually relevant to browsers and search engine",
        options:[
            "To store information usually relevant to browsers and search engine",
            "To only store information usually relevant to browsers",
            "To only store information about search engines",
            "To store information about external links",

        ]

    },
    {
        numb:10,
        question:"What would be the colours of the RGB where the hexadecimal values are #FF0000, #00FF00 and #0000FF respectively?",
            
            answer:"Red, Green, Blue",
        options:[
            "Blue, Green, Red",
            "Green, Blue, Red",
            "Red, Blue, Green",
            "Red, Green, Blue",

        ]

    },
    {
        numb:11,
        question:"Identify the most accurate statement about the application of XML:",
        answer:"XML is used to describe hierarchically organized information",
        options:[
            "XML must be used to produce XML and HTML output",
            "XML cannot specify or contain presentation information",
            "XML is used to describe hierarchically organized information",
            "XML performs the conversion of information between different e-business applications",

        ]

    },
    {
        numb:12,
        question:`Which of the following attribute is used for merging two or more adjacent columns?`,
answer:"Colspan",
        options:[
            "Rowspan",
            "CellSpacing",
            "Colspan",
            "CellPadding",

        ]

    },
    {
        numb:13,
        question:"While working on a JavaScript project, in your JavaScript application, which function would you use to send messages to users requesting for text input?",
        answer:"Prompt()",
        options:[
            "Display() ",
            "Prompt()",
            "Alert() ",
            "Confirm()",

        ]

    },
    {
        numb:14,
        question:"Which property does one use to align text to the right side of a block-level element in Cascading Style Sheets?",
        answer:"text-align",
        options:[
            "horizontal-align ",
            "align ",
            "block-align ",
            "text-align",

        ]

    },
    {
        numb:15,
        question:"When is the content of a table shown?",
        answer:"After the table is loaded",
        options:[
            "Before the border loads",
            "After the table is loaded",
            "In pieces as it loads",
            " None of the above",

        ]

    },
    {
        numb:16,
        question:"A website is a_____cookie.",
        answer:"Transient",
        options:[
            "Volatile",
            "Transient",
            "In transient",
            "Non-volatile",

        ]

    },
    {
        numb:17,
        question:"Can negative values be allowed in padding property?",
        answer:"No",
        options:[
            "Yes",
            "No",
            "Depends on propery",
            "none",

        ]

    },
    {
        numb:18,
        question:"Which of the following JavaScript cannot do?",
        answer:"All of the Above",
        options:[
            "JavaScript can react to events",
            "JavaScript can manipulate HTML elements",
            "JavaScript can be use to validate data",
            "All of the Above",

        ]

    },
    {
        numb:19,
        question:"what does PoP stand for?",
        answer:"post office protocol",
        options:[
            "pre office protocol",
            "post office protocol",
            "protocol of post",
            "none",

        ]

    },
    {
        numb:20,
        question:"what is the number of layers in a OSI model?",
        answer:"7 layers",
        options:[
            "2 layers",
            "4 layers",
            "7 layers",
            "9 layers",

        ]

    },
    {
        numb:21,
        question:"the full form of OSI is?",
        answer:"open system interconnection",
        options:[
            "operating system interface",
            "optical system interconnection",
            "operating system internet",
            "open system interconnection",

        ]

    },
 
    {
        numb:22,
        question:"identify the layer which provides service to the user.",
        answer:"application layer",
        options:[
            "session layer",
            "application layer",
            "presentation layer",
            "physical layer",

        ]

    },
 
    {
        numb:23,
        question:"what is a hub?",
        answer:"network device",
        options:[
            "software",
            "computing device",
            "network device",
            "calculating device",

        ]

    },
 
    {
        numb:24,
        question:"what does a set of rules define.",
        answer:"protocol",
        options:[
            "SMTP",
            "FTP",
            "IMAP",
            "protocol",

        ]

    },
 
    {
        numb:25,
        question:"Which of the following protocol is used for remote terminal connection service?",
        answer:"TELNET",
        options:[
            "RARP",
            "UDP",
            "FTP",
            "TELNET",

        ]

    },
 
    {
        numb:26,
        question:"Which of the following terms is just a collection of networks thet can be joined together?",
        answer:"intranet",
        options:[
            "intranet",
            "extranet",
            "internet",
            "LAN",

        ]

    },
 
    {
        numb:27,
        question:"Bluetooth is an example of",
        answer:"Personal area network",
        options:[
            "Wide area network",
            "Virtual private network",
            "local area network",
            "Personal area network",

        ]

    },
    {
        numb:28,
        question:"The application layer of OSI model is",
        answer:"Seven layer",
        options:[
            "Four layer",
            "Five layer",
            "Six layer",
            "Seven layer",

        ]

    },
    {
        numb:29,
        question:"FDDI is",
            
            answer:"Ring network",
        options:[
            "Bus based network",
            "Mesh network",
            "Star network",
            "Ring network",

        ]

    },
    {
        numb:30,
        question:"Who invent WWW?",
        answer:"tim berners lee",
        options:[
            "bobkahn",
            "tim berners lee",
            "vintcerf",
            "lady adalovalace",

        ]

    },
 
]

const ansArray = []

questions.forEach(element => {
    ansArray.push(element.answer)
});

module.exports = ansArray